<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Software Engineering (I)</title><link>https://cpit251.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Software Engineering (I)</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 07:54:32 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cpit251.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Assignment 1</title><link>https://cpit251.github.io/assignments/assignment-1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 07:54:32 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://cpit251.github.io/assignments/assignment-1/</guid><description>Assignment 1: Scrum Watch the following video series from Atlassian on Scrum and answer the following questions:
What is Agile? What is Scrum? What is the product backlog? Who maintains it? What are the daily stand-ups in Scrum? How long are they often conducted? What are sprints? How are they planned? What is the difference between sprint reviews and retrospectives? What is the role of the Scrum master? Submit a PDF file with your answers by the due date (one hour before next class).</description></item><item><title>Lab 1</title><link>https://cpit251.github.io/labs/lab-1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 10:00:36 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://cpit251.github.io/labs/lab-1/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Course Syllabus</title><link>https://cpit251.github.io/syllabus/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 14:09:23 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://cpit251.github.io/syllabus/</guid><description>CPIT-251 Software Engineering (I) Credits: 3 credit hours Prerequisite: CPIT-250
Description The objective of this course is to study software engineering principles and techniques used in the specification, design, and testing of software systems. Major software development methodologies are reviewed including requirements, analysis and specification, design, testing, and documentation.
Course Learning Outcomes By completion of the course the students should be able to:
Describe the need for and importance of software engineering and its objectives.</description></item><item><title>Git</title><link>https://cpit251.github.io/examples/git/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 07:39:02 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://cpit251.github.io/examples/git/</guid><description>Introduction</description></item><item><title>Miscellaneous</title><link>https://cpit251.github.io/miscellaneous/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 11:59:35 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://cpit251.github.io/miscellaneous/</guid><description>This webpage contains a list of useful tools and resources you may need in web development.
IDE and Text Editors You&amp;rsquo;ll need an IDE or a text editor to manage all the code you write. Below is a list of widely used IDE and text editors:
Visual Studio Code (VS Code) an excellent code editor for Mac, Windows, and Linux. For Java, you may use a text editor with a plugin or an IDE.</description></item></channel></rss>